NABEEL AL GEFARY

Mobile App Developer

phone 963+ 967122753 Email: nabgef@gmail.com

Address: Syria - Damascus LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nabeel-gefary-955020207/

Experience:

SaidLite Company: Flutter Developer | [2021 - 2022]

- Developed mobile applications with Flutter based on UI/UX designs in Adobe XD and Figma..
- Integrated backend services with mobile applications, enhancing app functionality and performance.
- Utilized Dart language for app logic and collaborated with teams to create responsive and animated interfaces.

AxtroSoft Company: Flutter Developer | [2022 - 2023]

- Implemented Firebase services, including push notifications, background services, and dynamic linking, enhancing user engagement.
- Applied GetX state management for efficient app state handling and navigation.

SDNone Company: Flutter Developer | [2023 - Now]

- Integrated Pusher and Socket.IO for real-time communication features in mobile apps.
- Used BLoC state management for maintaining application state, improving code structure and reusability.
- Deployed apps on Google Play, Apple Store, Huawei Store, and Amazon Store.
- Worked with Google Maps and Mapbox for location-based services.
- Integrated local storage solutions using Shared Preferences,
 SQFLite, Hive, and GetStorage.

Projects:

Summary:

Mobile App Developer with over 3 years of experience in building production-level mobile applications using Flutter and Dart. Proficient in Firebase, RESTful APIs, real-time communication, and state management. Experienced in app deployment across various platforms with a focus on optimizing app performance and user experience..

Education:

Damascus University - ITE Started: 2018
Graduated: 2023

KEY SKILLS:

- Problem Solving
- Team Collaboration
- Git/Version Control
- Clean Code
- Agile Software
- Time Management
- Flexibility

Achievements:

- Certificate of experience in a SDNone Company
- Material Components
 Certificate from Google
 Cloud (Coursera)

- Moovo App Developed a user-friendly ecommerce app enabling customers to browse products, add items to cart, and complete secure payments. Integrated features like product search, and push notifications to enhance user experience.
 - **App Demo**: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1JrD1yKTLEUGqSPHTOuJi5SAr6LTSjRTK/view?usp=sharing
- **Swess Home** Real estate app covering properties in Damascus and its countryside. Features agent listings and extensive property coverage.

App Link: https://apps.apple.com/us/app/swess-home/id1591728350

 Eavando App Online store for selling clothes and fashion with electronic payment features.

App Link: https://apps.apple.com/be/app/eavando/id6448908064

- 7RM APP Online booking services for quality horse events in the UAE.
 App Link: https://apps.apple.com/ae/app/sevenrm/id6475645542
- Mazad Alnokhba: E-commerce app with multi-stores for animal-related products.
 App Link: https://apps.apple.com/in/app/mazad-alnokhba/id1597116939
- Ryan Customer Captain: Driver taxi app allowing customers to book taxi cars.
 App Link (Driver): https://apps.apple.com/in/app/rayan-driver/id6451476305
 App Link (Customer): https://apps.apple.com/kw/app/rayan-customer/did1621499233
- WeSafe: Trips Management App helps employees to manage your tasks and trips and organizes it. in addition to monitors their works efficiency.
 App Link: https://apps.apple.com/us/app/we-safe/id6736458367
- Clinics Assistant: Application for managing clinic reservations.
 (My Graduation Project)

App Demo: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1R-HCnBfB9VvwfB7UiM0yj4ldASvlM3Bx /view?usp=sharing

- **Gas Express:** Ecommerce for Gas products with admin dashboard and delivery App. **App Demo** https://drive.google.com/file/d/1bCLh5 75CG99BtW00DuLG5W0Z2EM8TdH

/view?usp=sharing

LANGUAGES:

- Arabic (Native)
- English (Intermediate).

Training and Courses:

- Udemy Courses (Mobile Development)
- Self-directed training.
- Flutter Development at Coursera